# JESUS MORALES JR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

# **Summary**

Full Stack Developer focused on delivering high-quality production-ready websites. Prior experience in customer service (3+ years) and management (1+ years) focusing on customer satisfaction. Three years of experience in web development through tech. schools and self-taught.

### **Education**

Lambda School

Aug. 2019 to Current

Full Stack Web Development

**Udacity** 

Sept. 2017 to July 2018

Full Stack Web Development

Thousand Oaks HighSchool

Aug. 2012 to June 2016

# **Projects**

### **Location Lookup**

location-lookup.jesusmj.com

The motivation behind this app was to gather information quickly from a location.

React | Axios | Material-UI | Sass

#### Clicker Game

clicker-game.jesusmj.com

This is a simple click-to-win game.

React | Anime.is | Material-UI | Sass

### **Rick and Morty Siting**

rick-and-morty.jesusmj.com

Grabs all characters and locations from an API and displays them. React | Axios | Material-UI | Sass

## **Employment**

McDonald's

Manager

Thousand Oaks, California Feb. 2016 to Mar. 2018

Arby's Cashier Thousand Oaks, California June 2018 to Aug. 2019

### **Contact**

- jmjles@gmail.com
- jesusmj.com
- **\$ 8058259190**
- **♥** Thousand Oaks, California
- in jesus-morales
- n imiles

### **Skills**

#### LANGUAGES

HTML5

CSS3

**Javascript** 

SQL

Sass

#### **LIBRARIES**

React.js

**Jquery** 

Anime.js

Redux

Node.is

Axios.is

#### DATABASES

MongoDB

MySQL

**PostgreSQL** 

#### **FRAMEWORKS**

Express.js

Material-Ul